Deep in the Congo, Marine... Peace Keeper... Killer.
Sniper: Reloaded is a war, action, thriller film directed by Claudio Fäh.
Marine Sgt.
Brandon Beckett, son of the U.S.
Marine Corps' deadliest sniper, Thomas Beckett, must turn to his father's former protégé (Billy
Zane) to track down and kill a mysterious sniper before he kills his next target.
Brandon Beckett, played by Chad Michael Collins.
Colonel Ralf Jäger, played by Richard Sammel.
Lt. Ellen Abramowitz, played by Annabel Wright.
Richard Miller, played by Billy Zane.
Vincent "The Italian" Masiello, played by Justin Strydom.
Kyle Brown, played by Hlomla Dandala.
Sniper: Reloaded is a 2011 direct to video action film which was directed by Claudio Fäh and was
the fourth installment in the Sniper film series and a sequel to Sniper 3 (2004).
This film is the first in the series of Sniper that does not feature the
character of Thomas Beckett, who was portrayed by Tom Berenger.
Instead, it introduces his son Brandon, who was
portrayed by Chad Michael Collins.
Also, Billy Zane reprises his role as Richard Miller from the first film.
The film was shot from 1 March 2010 to 3 April 2010 on
location in Johannesburg, South Africa.
It was released on DVD on April 26, 2011.
The tone is emotional and intense.